Victor Velasquez | Developer

victorv24@gmail.com
619-929-5760

victorinspace.github.io/
in www.linkedin.com/in/victor-dev

I'm a front-end web developer based Las Vegas with a passion for learning and solving problems using creative solutions. I love component-based development and using OOP. I also have experience with Agile (Scrum) methodologies and using version control (Git).

Technical Skills:

➤ HTML5

➤ React JS

> Jquery

➤ CSS3

➤ Node JS

➤ Bootstrap4

➤ JavaScript ES6

➤ Git

➤ Agile/Scrum

Experience:

• **Nevada Corporate Headquarters** — Web Developer 11/2018 - 12/2018 Designed, developed and tested custom landing pages for company brands.

• **PunchCode** — Coding Bootcamp Student 5/2018 - Present 12-week intensive full stack web development training. The primary focus was on using JavaScript to build fully-functioning web applications using React JS.

• **Oto Float** — Junior IT Technician, Junior Developer 6/2016 - 3/2017 Handled software and hardware installations (ex: Raspberry Pi, IoT, Arduino).

• Lyynks – QA Analyst 8/2012 - 10/2014 Tested software and submitted detailed reports of issues using Pivotal Tracker.

Education:

•	PunchCode	Certificate — Front-End Web Development	2018
•	Platt College	Bachelor of Science — Media Arts	2008 - 2011
•	Platt College	Associate's Degree — Graphic Design	2007 - 2008

Projects:

• Food For Thought — (<u>bit.ly/food-for-thought-github</u>)

2018

o React JS

Redux

Express

o Chart JS

o Node JS

React Native

o MySQL

o Semantic UI

. O---1-M----

Google Maps API